you know i know so many people from cuba that were treated terribly and they're over here they
became rich they're very entrepreneurial people very smart know a lot from florida especially
there's so so many people friend of mine started over nothing he's now the largest owner of gas
stations in the country and stuff i mean cuban i i also know i i was just with a fantastic
person who's cuban and made a fortune in sugar you know fun whole family right and
this family wants to go back to cuba to visit it they wanted they haven't been back in like 50
years or something i think cuba is in its own way if they're you know tourism and everything else
it's a beautiful island great weather they're not in a hurricane zone which is nice for a change you
know they won't be asking us for money for hurricanes every week but uh but i think cuba
see the end you know all my life i've been hearing about the united states and cuba
when will the united states do it i do believe i'll be the honor of having the honor of
taking cuba that'd be good that's a big honor taking cuba taking cuba in some form yeah
taking cuba i mean whether i free it take it i think i could do anything i want with it you want
to know the truth they're a very uh weakened nation right now they were for a long time very violent
very violent leaders castro was a very violent leader his brother's a very violent leader
extremely violent that's how they governed they governed with violence but a lot of people would like to go
back